Allahu Akbar (God is Supreme) x4
La Elaha Ella Allah (There is no god except the one God.)
Alhamdu Lillah, Wa Ash-hadu Alla Elaha Ella Allah Wahdahu La Shareeka Lah.
We praise God and we bear witness that there is no god except the One God.
I will be just chatting with you since I did not really prepare anything.
And I want to talk about loving God.
A rhetorical question: Should we love God? And why?
And to understand this why we should love God and how much
The Quran describes the believers as loving God the most,
that is more than anything else.
And I will try to share with you the logical reasons why we should, we must love God.
So, if we go back in history, a few billion years, we had billions of creatures of God who were not classified.
They were not angels or humans or jinns yet.
It was God and His kingdom.
And then one of the creatures developed this blasphemous idea that challenged God's absolute authority.
Satan thought that he can be also a god,
he has enough power and enough qualifications, he thought, for him to serve as a god in his own right.
So, he initiated this blasphemy.
Among the creatures were some who were also as egotistic and as proud, almost, as egotistic and as proud as Satan.
And they said to themselves yeah.
Satan, those creatures were almost equal, almost, there were some stronger than others by virtue of whatever God gave them.
But they thought that yes Satan has enough qualities, enough qualifications to be a god besides God.
These creatures were also egotistic.
They had ego. They had pride.
And subconsciously they were thinking that yes we too, you know, we're close to Satan. We're almost equal.
So, we too can be gods maybe, but this was all in their heads.
So, they committed the blasphemy but not to the same extent as Satan.
They blasphemed against God.
They thought mentally that they can challenge, or they challenged His absolute authority.
Now, God's absolute authority is not an egotistic practice on the part of God, SUBHANAHU WA TA'AALAA, may He be glorified,
but because it is the truth.
The truth is that only God can run a kingdom where He is the God.
This is the truth.
The truth is that there is no one else who can run a kingdom.
So, God decided, as we've been talking about this to put Satan to the test.
He said the one who initiated the blasphemy will, will... I will make him a god and see what he can do.
Prove that he is incompetent, that he cannot do it.
Because this is the best way to find out.
If you claim to be able to fly a plane, the best thing to find out is to put you in a plane and say here, go ahead and fly.
And this is what God decided to do with Satan
And all those creatures who agreed with Satan were destined to become his subjects and to witness his incompetence.
And suffer his incompetence, as a matter of fact.
But anyway, God, now at this moment, the creatures became classified.
The creatures who without hesitation, without any question accepted God's absolute authority, they became angels
or they were angels.
Satan who challenged God's absolute authority became a jinn
became a fallen angel.
He received a judgement, a sentence, to be confined to the innermost universe,
This comes later, of course.
and to be put to the test.
And then, his descendents, Satan's descendents are all the jinns.
And the creatures who mentally agreed with Satan are you and me, became humans.
These became the human beings.
Now, the angels, as you know from the Quran, from Sura number 2, when God said I am gonna put Satan to the test.
I am gonna send these creatures, give them a second chance.
God is giving us a second chance to denounce the blasphemy of challenging His absolute authority,
and to come now in these circumstances where we start it clean. We're born into this world, forgetting everything else, starting all over again.
And now we can denounce any SHIRK, any idea of having another god besides God
and believe in the absolute authority of God alone.
If we can do this, then we go back to the kingdom of God.
So, God willed that we get another chance.
What did the angels say?
They said send them all to Hell.
That's what the angels said.
They said are You gonna put on earth those who are going to corrupt it and shed blood?
Remember that from Sura number 2?
So, in effect what are they saying?
God said I'm going to give these creatures a chance to come back to Me.
The angels said send them all to Hell.
Should we love God or not?
If it were up to the angels who believed in God's absolute authority, we will be now in Hell.
There would be no test, no seven universes, no planet earth.
It will be just Hell.
We'll be dismissed from God's Kingdom.
And you and I will be now in Hell.
But God who describes Himself as Arrahman Arraheem, the Most Gracious, Most Merciful said I'm giving them another chance to come to Me.
You think we should love God?
Should you not love God for that?
This is why we should love God.
I just found some basis for this.
I mean, we find this dispute in the High Society in Sura 38, verse 69.
And I also found traces of it, maybe not even traces, maybe the same thing in the Bible, in the previous scripture.
Romans 3:23, which is a multiple of 19, chapter 3, verse 23, as you know, ...
guess I didn't write the verse here,
talks about,
Oh, yeah, ok, I didn't write it here, but now I remember it.
It says we have all sinned.
Talks about the fact that we have all sinned.
We have all challenged God's absolute authority.
We have committed a crime. This is why we are here.
A terrible, terrible crime for which the angels saw that we should go to Hell right away.
You probably have seen this in Roman 6:23 where it says, the wages of sin is death
Very famous statement: the wages of sin is death.
Because what happened as a consequence of this rebellion, Satan's rebellion and yours and mine,
the system that God designed called for putting all those creatures to death.
You and I were dead before we came here.
And that God created death, as a consequence of that blasphemy.
So, the wages of sin is death.
It comes from that origin.
And then in Hebrews 1:3, we read that talks about purging our sins.
Purging our sins means denounce our idolatry,
Idolatry being the idea that there may be a god besides God.
So that we could become sons of God
which means going back to the Kingdom of God.
Tooboo Ela Allah. Repent. Let's try to get back.
Alhamdu Lillah. We praise God,
Wa Ash-hadu Alla Elaha Ella Allah Wahdahu La Shareeka Lah.
And we bear witness that there is no god except He.
We committed that blasphemy
and to put it bluntly, the angels said send them all to Hell.
And God said I know what you don't know.
God said I am gonna give them another chance.
But when we look around us, we see how bad we are
how bad the human race is.
They're so bad, it's not even funny.
They're so bad.
There is not a single mosque in the world, other than this mosque and a few associated with it, where God is commemorated alone,
where God is the absolute God.
Every single mosque in the world is violating the commandment in 72:18 that says:
The mosque belongs to God, do not call on any other name but His name.
And try to tell, try to ask them to say, La Elaha Ella Allah, There is no god except God.
We have a mosque right here. Let's try it.
Let's go there and tell them. I mean,
it's not even three miles from here.
Tell them La Elaha Ella Allah (There is no go except God)
and they beat you up.
They will actually get violent.
That's a typical mosque.
And they beat you up because we're in America here because this is civilized world.
Over there, they'll kill you
for saying La Elaha Ella Allah (There is no god except God).
No kidding!
They're so bad.
Every church in the world, the biggest ones, the cathedrals, all those beautiful buildings, they're all blaspheming against God saying:
Jesus God or son of God, or the father, the son, the holy spirit.
See, this is who we are.
Initially we challenged God's absolute authority.
And we are the few that God told the angels I know what you do not know.
I was writing a footnote in the new translation on why did God allow two verses, false verses to be injected in the Quran for 1400 years.
Why did He permit it for 1400 years?
And it's because just a few years after the prophet's death, they reverted to idolatry.
The Muslims reverted to idolatry.
Only this time around, their idol was the prophet who defeated them.
The prophet won the war, and they became Muslims.
But a few years later, they reverted to idolatry.
They did not deserve the Quran.
And they killed Ali and his family which is the prophet's family.
They killed the prophet's family because of these two verses.
And I have the documents. You're gonna see the documents in the footnote.
I didn't mean to get into this subject but since I got into it...
During the time of Uthman,
the Khalifa formed a committee to make copies of the Quran,
take the original Quran that the prophet wrote with his own hand,
make copies from it and send it to the new lands.
They opened new lands in Syria, Iraq and so on
and they wanted to send these copies there.
Now, Sura 9 was the last Sura revealed in Medina.
The prophet had written all these Suras with the instructions as to where each one goes.
And that so, one of the scribes or maybe two suggested since these copies are going to new lands, let us honor our prophet
and add a couple of verses praising him.
Ali was a member of that committee.
The members were Uthman, who's the supervisor, he was the Khalifa. He was just talking. Ali was a member. Zeid Ibn Thaabet was a member and Ubayy Ibn Ka‘ab was a member, and maybe some others.
So, when the suggestion came up, Ali was outraged.
And then, as a consequence of that suggestion, Uthman was killed, Ali became the Khalifa.
The supporters of the two verses waged war on Ali.
Fifty years of war came after that because of these two verses.
And they culminated in the battle of Karbala where Hussein and the whole family of the prophet were wiped out, except for women and children.
They killed them all.
And then the first ruler to come after this war was Marwan Ibn Al Hakam.
The first thing he did was what? He burnt the Quran that Muhammad wrote with his own hand.
He was afraid war will start all over again.
So, these people did not deserve the true Quran.
And for the last 1400 years,
there was not... I mean, I'm astounded that we came to this conclusion by God's grace that we shall worship God Alone, that we follow the Quran.
And God is giving us a present, gifts.
God is flooding us with presents including the true Quran,
which should be printed, IN SHAA ALLAH, for the first time in 1400 years.
We're going to have the true Quran without the two false verses.
And I have now the footnote available for any of you to read the evidence, all the proof and it is irrefutable
about the two verses.
In the last few weeks, Abdullah and Mahmood have been busy.
The pipeline had been open through them, and Ihsan.
And the proof has been coming very fast.
Just so to be included in that footnote.
It's unbelievable.
Abdullah walked in with some more miracles this afternoon.
I thought I was printing the final footnote.
He said it's not the final.
So, those people... God permitted those two verses because they did not deserve the Quran.
They're so bad that we will understand the verses.
In Sura 22, verses 19 to 22, they say that
- These are very harsh verses,
and if you see those people, you will understand that God is very Merciful to punish them just that much in Hell.
They say... these verses say that clothes of fire will be tailored for them.
Something like Sulphuric acid be poured on top of their head,
-the sulphuric acid of the Hereafter which is much stronger than the one we have now-
that will melt their inside out.
They will be confined in pots of iron or cells of iron.
Whenever they want to leave from the misery, they'll be forced back in,
I mean they're very harsh verses.
But when you meet these people, you'll see that God is Merciful.
because they insisted on going to that retribution,
but they really deserve a lot worse.
We met one of them, as I told you in the last KHUTBA, in Los Angles,
when just before me came a professor from Chicago theological institute,
to tell us that the Quran is hallucination of Muhammad, internal hallucination of Muhammad,
that it is fallible.
And then, I came immediately after him, presenting physical irrefutable evidence that the Quran is divine and it's from God.
Then, these people, some Arabs, so-called Muslims,
they stood up and attacked me.
They didn't attack they guy who said the Quran is internal hallucination.
And you look at them and you know that this punishment is not enough for them,
that God is very Merciful.
Really, I mean, if I am going to oppose somebody and I'm a Muslim,
and I hear someone say that Quran is internal hallucination, I will change my plan.
I will attack the guy who says Quran is hallucination
and I will take this fellow on the side and beat him up with something, but on the side, not in public.
They didn't do that.
On the Day of Judgement, they will call on the guardian of Hell, Mãlek,
and they will say tell your Lord to finish us off.
And Mãlek will say sorry, you're gonna last forever.
Because they insisted on it.
This, in Sura 40, it says that these people argue with falsehood to defeat the truth.
And these people came with, I mean, what is clearly falsehood.
They came with things fixed in their mind.
They say you counted the letter in this way, but they should be counted in another way,
which is a wrong way.
However, when I presented the paper, I gave them numbers, not even letters.
They can take the letters, but they should have changed their minds then, because there's no argument against the numbers.
If you take all the numbers in the Quran and add them up, you have a multiple of 19.
This has nothing to do with letters.
But God says the reason they insisted on going to hell,
and the reason they're subjected to that terrible retribution which is not enough for them,
is because we have given them the truth, but they hated the truth.
Aqem Al-Salat.